The Lost Princess is a action, adventure film directed by Hicham Hajji.
After an Ayahuasca vision transports him to a haunted castle, Alec meets Hanna who tales him the story of her mother's forced
marriage and how the forbidden passion with her father was in danger when the princess pregnancy became obvious
Alec Touati, played by Cillian O'Sullivan.
Nassim Ikken, played by Gary Dourdan.
Robert Goodman, played by Robert Knepper.
Princess Nour, played by Soraya Azzabi.
The Shaman, played by Eric Roberts.
Nina, played by Irma Lake.
2025 in film is an overview of events, including award ceremonies, festivals, a list of
country- and genre-specific lists of films released, and notable deaths.
Shochiku and Gaumont celebrated their 130th anniversaries; 20th Century Studios and Republic Pictures
celebrated their 90th anniversaries; and Studio Ghibli celebrated its 40th anniversary.
Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer's first musical film The Broadway Melody (1929), known for being the first sound
film to win the Academy Award for Best Picture, entered the public domain this year.